[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Here's the latest news.
Ching He's chairman, Huang, has died today while in custody
in connection with the high-profile case.
Initial findings point to a myocardial infarction.
An autopsy has ruled out homicide.
Officials have not yet confirmed these reports.
It is unclear how Huang's sudden death will impact the investigation.
We will bring you updates as this story develops.
Next,
Mayor-elect Tristan Hsueh is set to take office.
Ahead of the inauguration, he attended a charity event today.
Tristan Hsueh emphasized
that citizens will come first in future policy.
Goddamn it.
You traitors.
No honor.
They say one thing to your face and another behind your back.
Don't be so angry.
Young people today aren't like we used to be.
Forget about honor.
Be grateful if they don't backstab you.
Fuck.
I saw him as a brother, but he treated me like dirt.
Fuck him!
We want to create a society
defined by kindness and doing what's right.
Transforming a city takes more than just the mayor.
It requires our collective wisdom and effort.
THE FIXERS
PRIMORDIAL FILES
Mayor, congratulations on taking office.
Thank you. Everyone's hard work got us to where we are today.
You have our full support.
-Congratulations, Mayor Hsueh. -Hi, Ms. Lu.
-You surpassed the master. -Thanks.
Your father has a successor now.
My dad always tells me to learn from you.
Don't say that.
We're counting on you moving forward, mayor.
Let's catch up another time.
Sure, we'll talk soon.
How are you?
Getting used to it?
These occasions make me wonder
if good acting is nature
or nurture.
I know you don't like these occasions.
How's the key thing going?
It's all set.
Just the ceremony.
Come with me.
-Minister. -Hi, mayor.
Let me introduce.
This is my brother, Louis Hsueh.
-Hello, Louis. -Hello.
I look forward to your support.
Sure, no problem.
DOUBLE HAPPINESS
CHING HE TEMPLE OF TZU YUN CLIFF
MAYOR, TRISTAN HSUEH, MING YOUNG PARTY
Ching He Temple has always been a place where citizens gather in faith and virtue.
Today I came here to pray in the hope that
this new chapter at Ching He Temple
will bring us good luck.
Welcome back.
These two keys are yours to keep now,
chairwoman.
You've worked hard lately, Sir Hong.
Get some rest.
So, on behalf of my cabinet,
I pray that our upcoming initiatives will run smoothly
and bring greater prosperity to everyone.
CELESTIAL
You must take back the position
that belongs to you.
Only you
are qualified to be Fixer Celestial.
Make both sides of the law
fear you…
and respect you.
After entering Kuang Ming Chamber,
find the compass of Primordial Files.
Align the dials…
PRIMORDIUM
…in this specific order.
East, Frost's Descent.
FROST'S DESCENT
West, year 1909.
YEAR 1909
South, morning hours five to seven.
MORNING HOURS 5 TO 7
True North.
TRUE
With this passcode,
you can enter the secret tunnel to the Primordial Files.
This date marks the day Liao Tien-ting faked his death
and reemerged as the first Fixer Primordium.
Only Fixer Celestial and Fixer Primordium
have access to the secret tunnel.
Forced entry would trigger the destruction of the Primordial Files.
If the Primordial Files fall into the wrong hands…
If she reclaims Ching He,
she will have the Hsuehs by the throat.
…the balance of the world will be broken.
So we must get to the Primordial Files before her.
That way, we can control both sides of the law.
Neither Ching He nor Yeh Yueh Tong…
-If I take over, what about Madam Fan? -…can threaten the Hsuehs.
If that happens, I fear no one will be able to save it.
Leave that to the next head of Ching He.
Do you really think
the Hsuehs will spare those who know about their secret
if they find out about the video?
SEVERAL DAYS AGO
If the Primordial Files fall into the hands of those in the light,
their power will grow indefinitely.
If the Files fall to those in the dark,
crime will become more rampant.
Having them keep each other in check
is the only way to truly protect
the Hsueh family,
Ching He,
and your partner.
You're not wrong.
But you never had the Primordial Files, did you?
My brother said
only Madam Fan knows how to open the secret tunnel to the Primordial Files.
No wonder you want to trap her.
What are you going to do?
Damn it, it'll be harder next time.
Fuck!
Sir Hong,
are you a traitor too?
I came to thank you on behalf of the chairman.
Fixer Lunar will kill me for sure.
I need your help.
So you and the chairman set a trap
to get the Primordial Files from Madam Fan?
Fixer Gold stopped you from killing Lunar
for a reason.
So he was working with you two?
It might be better to let him explain.
Fucking bastard.
You kept us in the dark.
Otherwise, Madam Fan wouldn't have believed it.
I have a plan to get everyone out safely.
I need you on this.
Welcome back.
These two keys are yours to keep now,
chairwoman.
You've worked hard lately, Sir Hong.
Get some rest.
Hands up.
Get out of the car.
Madam Fan has returned to Ching He.
I advise you not to do this.
I'll ask one last time.
Where are the case files?
What do you want them for?
She is not only ruthless, but also swift.
I guessed right.
After all this time,
you still don't know her?
Even I know what kind of person she is.
Of those who have done dirty work for her,
how many are still alive?
Before you kill me,
think carefully.
Are you working for the right person?
PRIMORDIUM
Well, look at that.
Being mayor isn't enough.
You should have known.
I did.
Just not that you'd act so fast
and do it yourself.
I've learned my lesson.
If you want something done right,
do it yourself.
You think you can handle Ching He
without me?
The other six chairpersons
aren't easy to deal with.
Who says I want to take over Ching He?
You were right about having one in the dark and one in the light.
Louis Hsueh?
If you kill Ching He's chairperson in the Kuang Ming Chamber,
do you know what will happen?
I don't.
But the living will tell me.
Before you kill me…
let me go in and take a look.
Sorry, I can't do that.
I wouldn't have done this
if I had any other option.
Hello, mayor.
Mayor,
long time no see.
I just made tea. Come have a cup.
What is it?
Are you surprised the Primordial Tunnel led you back to Tai Sui Hall
or that I am here?
Sir Hong told me to give you this.
And this stamp.
After you take it, your heart will stop temporarily.
Please.
Since when did San He become Thackery's lackey?
You're invited to tea,
so fucking drink the tea.
We pay back in kind.
Chairman,
may I smoke?
Of course.
But you're the first.
So you've summoned these guys.
I'm not leaving today, am I?
Mayor,
whether you can leave or not is up to you.
Pin,
please take them to the temple entrance.
I don't want anyone to come in.
Mayor, here's the thing.
Don't be fooled by the tranquility here.
A storm is raging outside.
Everyone is busy.
You can't even hold a gun.
And you want to shoot?
Do you know what my symptoms are?
If I try to hold something still,
my hand shakes.
But if I keep moving,
it doesn't shake.
Fatass.
Fuck you!
Look on my works, ye Mighty, and despair.
This one shot is the peak of my career.
Chi…
I fucking did it.
You set me up.
So the Primordial Entrance was fake?
We originally wanted Madam Fan
to walk through the tunnel.
CELESTIAL
PRIMORDIUM
So you've been working together?
I dealt with Madam Fan
so you could take control of Ching He.
But you teamed up with Thackery to betray me.
This is from Hsu Ming-yi's dashcam.
You lied to me.
Dad didn't kill Hsu Ming-yi.
This should be enough, right?
Sir,
what do you take me for?
I'm not after money.
So what do you want?
I've been an aide all these years
so I could eventually become a legislator.
But I'm a nobody.
I can't get elected.
But if…
If the Hsueh family is willing to back me,
I'll have a chance.
Is that a threat?
If the juicy scoop on the Hsuehs's role in the Hsin Nan redevelopment project
got leaked,
do you think
you could still stand here
and negotiate with me?
Do you know how hard I worked
to get to where I am today?
That's why I say
work with me, so we both win.
Think about it.
Hello, sweetie.
It's fine. I'm enjoying my chat with the councilor.
Okay, I'll be back soon.
Don't worry.
I know.
Fuck!
Negotiating with me?
Hello? Honey?
What's wrong? What was that sound?
What happened--
You were worried this would get out,
so you went to Yeh Yueh Tong
to erase every trace of you
and get rid of everyone who knows about this.
You were never trying to cover up Dad's scandal.
You were trying to save your political career.
Do you think I got this far
by doing nothing?
In everyone's eyes,
I'm just Jerome Hsueh's puppet.
No one can see my accomplishments.
Hsu Ming-yi thought he had some dirt on me
and could use me as a stepping stone.
Unlike you,
I can't afford any mistakes.
Dad has no idea, right?
You know, sometimes I really envy you.
You can do whatever you want.
I just never expected
that the one to stab me in the back
would be my own brother.
This is the only way to strike a three-way balance
between Ching He and the Hsuehs.
You teamed up with Ching He, and now you talk about balance?
I found this in the Primordial Files.
CASE FILE, DOUBLE SHADOW TOP SECRET, THACKERY HUANG
I was going to use secrets from the Primordial Files
as leverage to balance the scales.
CASE FILE, JIANGNAN, PRIMORDIUM, 1984 CELESTIAL ACCESS ONLY
But I found something about you, Fixer Solar.
CASE FILE, DOUBLE SHADOW TOP SECRET, THACKERY HUANG
Back then, you asked Fixer Primordium
to conveniently frame Madam Fan's dad for the death of a fixer.
However, we discovered
that the murder of Ching He's fixer
is connected to you.
So we must postpone
handing over the position of Fixer Celestial to your daughter.
And this is just one of your dirty deeds.
No wonder you wanted the Primordial Files.
So you could destroy them, right?
If this information got leaked,
what would top officials and other branches think?
I never thought you would threaten me.
The third party you mentioned
is you, isn't it?
It's not a threat.
It's balance.
If any one party wants to disrupt this balance,
they will have to pay the price.
Since we were kids, I've always known you were smart.
That's why I'd rather you fool around than get serious.
Because I knew that once you got serious, you would become my biggest problem.
So Ching He will be counting on the Hsueh family from now on.
Do I have a choice?
One set the trap,
and the other sprung it.
I was just going with the flow.
This pawn put me in check too.
You truly are better than me at everything.
I've said it before.
I'll help the family one day,
but in my own way.
Howie,
tell your mom that it's all good now.
You didn't see how cool your dad was just now.
I'll come get you guys later. We're going home.
You escaped again?
What?
Did you miss me?
I couldn't be happier to be rid of you.
Get in.
I bought you bread.
Are you trying to trick me again?
It takes a lot to knock me down.
If I flop,
I'll crawl back without shame.
Nobody gets out without a few scars.
We'll get back in the game if this gig falls apart.
Scallion is always the best.
ARCADE
What's next for you?
I want to go abroad to study
and start afresh.
What will you do about Madam Fan's death?
Others will only think that Madam Fan is missing.
What about you?
Are you gonna stay with Ching He?
I'm the only one neither side will touch.
If I don't stay, the balance of terror won't last.
Aren't you stuck, then?
Should I sell noodles with you?
You could.
Turns out you're the one who can't just walk away.
I should go.
See you again.
I'm leaving Ben's stall to you.
Take good care of it for me.
Hey. Not gonna go after her?
What for? Are we in a romantic drama?
Shouldn't you go see a doctor?
I'm waiting for a ride.
Let's go.
You're so fussy, jeez.
To maintain that balance, you need the dark, the light, and the in-between.
Is this the excuse you've come up with for your brother?
Delete all the closed case files in Yeh Yueh Tong.
Ching He has leverage over Tristan Hsueh.
I have leverage over Ching He.
This is the only way to achieve true balance.
Are you telling me this
as Ching He's Fixer Gold
or as the Hsueh family's younger son?
Louis Hsueh.
I don't know if you can still hear me.
If you knew, you would definitely say that I betrayed Tristan.
All my life, I'd wanted to prove that I was no worse than him.
But after so much, I realized
it wasn't worth my time at all.
If you see Mom after you leave us,
please be nicer to her.
Fixer Lucky, your departure will be a great loss to Ching He.
And you've just gotten your touch back.
Why do you want to…
It's time to retire.
I don't know when my disease will worsen.
And my son will be in high school soon.
Kids stop calling once they're in college.
I only have three more precious years with him.
That's true.
But honestly, if you hadn't helped,
Ching He wouldn't have gotten back on its feet.
You hear that?
Hey, Sir Hong.
Is your arm all right?
It's fine. I will survive.
This sum will be enough for a comfortable life after you retire.
But remember--
Don't disclose anything about Ching He.
Of course.
Don't worry.
I'll come here to pray and have tea whenever I'm free, so don't miss me.
Get out of here already.
-I'll walk you out. -Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you, chairman.
Thank you, Sir Hong.
-Take care. -Take care.
Take care.
If you're bored someday,
come pick up a gig for extra cash.
When you're bored, come to my place.
I'll cook something nice for you.
Maybe I'll come tomorrow.
Oh, right.
Roses are red, violets are blue. What comes next?
Damn.
Still just as uncultured.
I'll take you down a peg or two.
AUTHENTIC TIEN-BU-LA
FELIX'S STIR-FRIED SWAMP EEL
-Hey, Howie. -Hey.
Come.
The noodles and tien-bu-la are for the back table.
Okay.
-How's that? -Holy cow.
Do your noodles taste that good?
You haven't gone under.
Hey, business is booming.
There's a line every day.
We have 4.9 stars on Google. You saw that?
Don't you start. You argue with customers online.
Don't think I didn't see that.
You can't blame me. They're difficult. They love my food but still complain.
All right.
I'll bring my boyfriend there next time.
Let me tell you, he's a great cook. He would put you to shame.
Hey, no.
When Howie's exams are done, we will travel to the US.
I'll cook for your foreign boyfriend.
Dummy, where will you find swamp eels here?
All right, see you. Bye.
Loach, check, please.
-I've got it. -Hey, no.
Milky shouldn't pay. On the house.
Hey.
-I'd feel bad about this. -It's fine.
Of course you would. You get it free every time.
Yeah, I really want to pay.
No need.
Gosh.
Hey, come again.
Bye.
Long time no see, Fixer Primordium.
PRIMORDIUM
Fixer Primordium
does not report to anyone, not even Fixer Celestial.
When Fixer Primordium shows up,
it means
something is about to go down in history.
Subtitle translation by: Hannah Liu